Guide to the Arlen Specter Senatorial Papers, Group 6. Public Relations and Media Files, 1972-2010 TJU.2010.01.06
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Press Office, 1981-2005; IV.
  - Press Releases, 1981-2005; 1.
    - 2000 (Box 1224, Folder 2)
      - Specter calls for "immediate action" to address increase in fuel prices, March 8, 2000; 21.
      - Specter suggests criminal prosecution for some Medicare fraud, March 9, 2000; 22.
      - Specter hails passage of bill bringing fairer treatment for families of air disaster victims, March 9, 2000; 23.
      - Senator Specter addresses concerns about his "report on the investigation of espionage allegations against Dr. Wen Ho Lee", March 9, 2000; 24.
      - Specter commends Albright for reaching out to people or Iran, March 17, 2000; 25.
      - Money not speech, Specter says, decrying Supreme Court opinion, March 28, 2000; 26.
      - Senators Specter and Biden call on President to take legal action against OPEC, March 30, 2000; 27.
      - Citing "travesties of justice" Specter urges oversight of espionage and other cases, April 4, 2000; 28.
      - Department of Justice may be guilty of obstructing justice, Specter charges, April 5, 2000; 29.
      - Senator Specter comments on Arctic National Wildlife Refuge vote, April 6, 2000; 30.
      - PA cable executive Gerry Lenfest announces $35 million gift to Mercersburg Academy, April 7, 2000; 31.
      - Specter wins additional $1.6 billion increase for NIH, April 7, 2000; 32.
      - Judiciary committee approves subpoenas for LaBella, Freeh campaign finance memos, April 13, 2000; 33.
      - Senator Specter did not change vote on Arctic National Wildlife Refuge, April 13, 2000; 34.
      - Judiciary Committee votes to subpoena for Charles LaBella to testify on Tuesday on campaign finance abuses, April 27, 2000; 35.
      - Specter writes Bush, defends Ridge, McCain against criticism from Pat Robertson, May 8, 2000; 36.
      - Labor, HHS, and education appropriations subcommittee boosts funds for NIH, Head Start, Job Corps, school grants, May 10, 2000; 37.
      - Specter announces $198,000 for high-risk adults in Delaware County, May 16, 2000; 38.
      - Senator Specter opposes permanent normal trade relations with China, May 16, 2000; 39.
      - Santorum and Specter announce funding for Carlisle barracks and Ft. Indiantown Gap, May 18, 2000; 40.
      - Santorum and Specter announce funding for 911th airlift wing, May 18, 2000; 41.
      - Specter asks Army Corps to investigate Philadelphia night club collapse, May 19, 2000; 42.
      - Governor Casey will be "sorely missed and long remembered," Senator Specter says, May 31, 2000; 43.
      - Quote on Dr. Heydt's retirement, June 6, 2000; 44.
      - President Assad "historic and great leader," Senator Specter said, June 10, 2000; 45.
      - Senators Specter and Santorum announce approval of $7 million for magnetic levitation system in Pittsburgh, June 13, 2000; 46.
      - Senators Specter and Santorum announce approval of $3 million for "smart highway" system, June 13, 2000; 47.
      - Senator Specter calls prospective airline merger a "big matter for Pennsylvania", June 14, 2000; 48.
      - Senate passes Specter legislation to spend $1 million on joint U.S.-Cuban drug interdiction, June 21, 2000; 49.
      - Specter says he has reasons to believe special counsel recommended to investigate Vice-President, June 22, 2000; 50.
      - Specter highlights LLHS bill, leads debate, June 22, 2000; 51.
      - Senators Santorum and Specter announce $445,000 in funding for National Heritage Corridor, June 22, 2000; 52.
      - Santorum and Specter announce funding for Rivers of Steel National Heritage Area, June 22, 2000; 53.
      - Senators Santorum and Specter announce funding for Brandywine battlefield, June 22, 2000; 54.
      - Contacting Senator Arlen Specter's press office, June 23, 2000; 55.
      - Judiciary Committee hearing opening statement excerpt, June 27, 2000; 56.
      - Senator Specter votes for substantial reduction in estate taxes, July 14, 2000; 57.
      - Senators Specter and Santorum announce preliminary approval of $7 million for Johnstown flood control, July 18, 2000; 58.
      - Senators Specter and Santorum announce full committee approval of $26.8 million for Delaware River deepening, July 18, 2000; 59.
      - Senators Specter and Santorum announce full committee approval of major Pittsburgh-area projects, July 18, 2000; 60.
      - Statement by Senator Arlen Specter: Senator Danforth report findings, July 21, 2000; 61.
      - Senators Specter and Santorum announce $1.4 million for Pittsburgh airport projects, July 26, 2000; 62.
      - Specter announces $4.8 million grant for revitalization of Martin Luther King, Jr. plaza, August 3, 2000; 63.
      - Specter announces $3.1 million for noise reduction at Lehigh Valley International Airport, August 4, 2000; 64.
      - Senator Specter calls Vice-President's speech tonight "most important" of political career, August 17, 2000; 65.
      - Senators Specter and Santorum announce release of $1 million for reverse commute initiatives in southeastern Pennsylvania, August 30, 2000; 66.
      - Senators Specter and Santorum announce $8 million in FAA grants for Pittsburgh airport rehab, September 5, 2000; 67.
      - Senator Specter calls for subpoenas on Ford, Bridgestone/Firestone tire problems, September 6, 2000; 68.
      - Senator Specter calls unilateral declaration of Palestinian statehood "a grave mistake", September 7, 2000; 69.
      - Senators Specter and Santorum announce $6.7 million in FAA grants for Philadelphia airport, September 12, 2000; 70.
      - Senators Specter and Santorum announce approval of $500,000 for Reading Berks emergency shelter, September 14, 2000; 71.
      - Senators Specter and Santorum announce funding for several Philadelphia area projects, September 14, 2000; 72.
      - Senators Specter, Biden introduce bill to televise Supreme Court arguments, September 21, 2000; 73.
      - Senator Arlen Specter announces funding for WVIA public television and radio station, September 27, 2000; 74.
      - Senators Specter and Santorum announce approval of $580,000 for Presque Isle peninsula development, September 27, 2000; 75.
      - Specter and Toomey announce 300,000 grant for youth work initiative, September 29, 2000; 76.
      - Senators Specter and Santorum announce federal funding for the Delaware and Lehigh Canal National Heritage Area, October 2, 2000; 77.
      - Senators Specter and Santorum announce federal funding for Lackawanna Heritage Area, October 2, 2000; 78.
      - Senators Specter and Santorum announce federal funding for Pennsylvania turnpike, October 3, 2000; 79.
      - Senators Specter and Santorum announce federal funding for Scranton/Wilkes-Barre projects, October 3, 2000; 80.
      - Santorum and Specter announce over $26 million for Pittsburgh area projects, October 3, 2000; 81.
      - Santorum and Specter announce $3 million in funding for Erie airport, October 3, 2000; 82.
      - Santorum and Specter announce $1.5 million for Fayette County airport, October 3, 2000; 83.
      - Santorum and Specter announce $1 million for Beaver County expressway travel center, October 3, 2000; 84.
      - Senators Specter and Santorum announce federal funding for several Philadelphia area projects, October 3, 2000; 85.
      - Senator Specter: "Score debate one for Bush", October 3, 2000; 86.
      - Senator Specter announces federal funding for Bethlehem intermodal facility, October 3, 2000; 87.
      - Senator Arlen Specter and Congressman Don Sherwood to address international flights and need for additional customs personnel at Wilkes-Barre/Scranton International Airport, October 9, 2000; 88.
      - Senator Specter on the Mideast situation: "What has to be done is every effort to make both sides back down and stop the violence", October 12, 2000; 89.
      - Senators Specter and Santorum announce $1 million for reverse commute initiatives in Pittsburgh, October 12, 2000; 90.
      - Specter: "We have a constitutional crisis in what is happening with the appropriations process", October 17, 2000; 91.
      - Senate passes resolution calling for immediate release of Edmond Pope, October 19, 2000; 92.
      - Senators Santorum and Specter announce $300,000 in funding to assist families in the Logan section of Philadelphia, October 19, 2000; 93.
      - Senators Santorum and Specter announce $300,000 in funding for redevelopment of DeShong Park, October 19, 2000; 94.
      - Santorum and Specter announce $700,000 for urban rivers awareness program in Philadelphia, October 19, 2000; 95.
      - Senators Specter and Santorum announce funding for several Philadelphia area projects, October 19, 2000; 96.
      - Specter: Constitution being ignored, October 19, 2000; 97.
      - VA to provide $13.6 million grant for Philadelphia veterans, Specter announces, October 23, 2000; 98.
      - Specter: Bush driving incident "has no relevancy", November 2, 2000; 99.
      - Specter introduces bill to create commission to study electoral voting procedures, November 14, 2000; 100.
      - Statement on Paul O'Neill, December 20, 2000; 101.
    - January-July 2001 (Box 1224, Folder 3)
      - Senator Specter comments on U.S. DOT selection of magnetic levitation system for Pittsburgh, January 18, 2001; 1.
      - Specter comments on academies cloning report, January 18, 2001; 2.
      - Senators Santorum, Specter announce $3 million for Indiana County coal workers, January 19, 2001; 3.
      - Specter named to committee assignments, January 25, 2001; 4.
      - Senators Specter and Harkin introduce act for comprehensive study of voting procedures, January 30, 2001; 5.
      - Senator Specter announces reasons for retaining chairmanship on the appropriations, labor, HHS, and education subcommittee, January 31, 2001; 6.
      - Senators Specter and Santorum announce $8.36 million in federal funding for Pittsburgh North Shore connector, February 5, 2001; 7.
      - Senator Specter joins bipartisan group in introducing managed care reform, February 6, 2001; 8.
      - Senator Specter comments on election of Sharon, February 6, 2001; 9.
      - Senator Specter favors tax plan requiring possible future tax cuts to be tied to minimum on-budget surplus, February 6, 2001; 10.
      - Specter secures Army Corps help to fix sinkholes, February 12, 2001; 11.
      - Specter comments on pardon hearing, February 13, 2001; 12.
      - Specter introduces biomedical revitalization resolution, February 13, 2001; 13.
      - Senator Specter sends steel caucus letter to the President regarding support of anti-dumping legislation, February 15, 2001; 14.
      - Kanjorski, Specter announce $250,000 grant for alternative learning center, February 20, 2001; 15.
      - Senator Specter and Secretary of Housing and Urban Development Mel Martinez tour Philadelphia housing development, February 21, 2001; 16.
      - Senator Specter reacts to speech by President Bush, February 27, 2001; 17.
      - Senator Specter chairs hearing on muscular dystrophy research, February 27, 2001; 18.
      - Senator Specter makes comments on OSHA ergonomics regulation, March 6, 2001; 19.
      - Senator Specter joins Senators from steel producing states in letter to the President seeking help for steel industry, March 5, 2001; 20.
      - Navy awards $9 million contract for laser guidance systems to Lockheed Martin, March 5, 2001; 21.
      - Senator Specter votes in favor of Brownfield's legislation, March 8, 2001; 22.
      - Senator Specter announces office expansion in Lehigh Valley, March 12, 2001; 23.
      - Senator Specter makes comments on campaign finance, steel imports, ergonomics, importation of trash, and family planning/Mexico City policy, March 13, 2001; 24.
      - Senator Specter makes comments on tax cuts, bankruptcy, and campaign finance, March 19, 2001; 25.
      - Specter supports repeal of global gag rule for international family planning organizations, March 20, 2001; 26.
      - Senator Specter joins in introduction of legislation on ergonomics rule making, March 22, 2001; 27.
      - Senator Specter announces community crime prevention grant, March 23, 2001; 28.
      - Senator Specter reintroduces bill to establish Valley Forge National Cemetery, March 26, 2001; 29.
      - Senator Specter makes comments on OSHA ergonomics regulation, March 29, 2001; 30.
      - Senator Specter introduces legislation in wake of pardon investigations, March 29, 2001; 31.
      - Senator Specter visits local fire station to assist with grant program, April 2, 2001; 32.
      - Senator Specter chairs hearing on Alzheimer's disease, April 3, 2001; 33.
      - Specter wins $700,000,000 increase in NIH funding, April 4, 2001; 34.
      - Specter continues push to allow federally funded researchers to derive stem cells, April 5, 2001; 35.
      - Senator Specter makes comments on his support for Bush tax cut/budget and the situation in China, April 6, 2001; 36.
      - Senator Specter urges President Bush to appoint special representative to Mideast, April 26, 2001; 37.
      - Senator Arlen Specter to meet with Geisinger Health System officials to discuss stroke care educational resource initiative, April 27, 2001; 38.
      - Senator Specter makes comments on retirement announcement of FBI Director Freeh, May 1, 2001; 39.
      - Senator Specter tours Good Shepherd works services facility, May 1, 2001; 40.
      - Senator Specter chairs hearing on the effect of Department of Labor practices on Amish communities, May 3, 2001; 41.
      - Santorum and Specter announce $23 million for stage II light rail in Allegheny County, May 8, 2001; 42.
      - Senator Specter makes comments on the release of FBI records in McVeigh case, May 11, 2001; 43.
      - Senator Specter to visit Russell for all-class reunion, May 16, 2001; 44.
      - Senator Specter makes comments on Senator Jeffords' decision to leave GOP, May 24, 2001; 45.
      - Senator Specter makes comments on tax bill, Senator Jeffords, rile of moderates, and steel, May 25, 2001; 46.
      - Senator Specter elected to key leadership position in GOP, May 25, 2001; 47.
      - Senator Specter makes comments on Senator Jeffords' decision to vote with Democrats on issue of organization, May 26, 2001; 48.
      - Senator Specter praises administration's announcement of 201 investigation for beleaguered steel industry, June 5, 2001; 49.
      - Senator Specter makes comments on United/U.S. Air merger, transfer of power in the Senate, and the execution of McVeigh, June 8, 2001; 50.
      - Senator Specter comments on current status of United/U.S. Airways merger, June 8, 2001; 51.
      - Santorum and Specter applaud funding for education initiatives in Philadelphia, June 11, 2001; 52.
      - Santorum and Specter applaud funding for teacher education initiative at Washington and Jefferson College, June 11, 2001; 53.
      - Senator Specter secures key hearing for Amish youth employment issue, June 13, 2001; 54.
      - Senator Specter makes comments on education bill, United/U.S. Air merger, and reorganization of Senate, June 15, 2001; 55.
      - Specter announces Lock Haven employees eligible for continued benefits, June 15, 2001; 56.
      - Specter applauds FBI effort resulting in Khobar Towers indictments, June 21, 2001; 57.
      - Senator Specter praises administration's announcement of start of 201 investigation into steel industry imports, June 22, 2001; 58.
      - Senator Specter makes comments on patients' bill of rights, FBI indictments, and United/U.S. Airways merger, June 22, 2001; 59.
      - Senator Specter announces support for prohibition of gambling on college sports, June 27, 2001; 60.
      - Senators Specter and Santorum announce funding for several Philadelphia area projects, June 29, 2001; 61.
      - Senator Specter makes comments on patients' bill of rights, Milosevic, Vice President Cheney's health, and Microsoft, June 29, 2001; 62.
      - Senators Specter and Santorum announce funding for Allegheny National Forest, June 29, 2001; 63.
      - Specter meets with U.S. Airways Chairman Wolf, July 10, 2001; 64.
      - Specter comments on decision by United/U.S. Air to seek ruling from Justice Department, July 12, 2001; 65.
      - Specter comments on meeting with FBI designate Mueller, July 12, 2001; 66.
      - Specter contacts Pate regarding U.S. Air/United, July 12, 2001; 67.
      - Senator Specter comments on latest developments on the U.S. Airways and United Airlines merger, stem cell research, and recent leadership meeting with President Bush, July 12, 2001; 68.
      - Specter and Santorum announce $2 million in funding for the Hershey Intermodal Transportation Center, July 13, 2001; 69.
      - Santorum and Specter announce over $37 million in funding for Pittsburgh area transportation projects, July 13, 2001; 70.
      - Santorum and Specter announce over $3 million in funding for Johnstown flood control project, July 13, 2001; 71.
      - Santorum and Specter announce over $40 million in funding for Monongahela River locks and dams and Saw Mill Run, July 13, 2001; 72.
      - Senators Specter and Santorum announce full committee approval of major southeastern-area projects, July 13, 2001; 73.
      - Santorum and Specter announce funding for Lehigh, Northampton, and Berks County projects, July 13, 2001; 74.
      - Senate transportation appropriations and energy appropriations funding announced for local projects, July 12, 2001; 75.
      - Senators Specter and Santorum announce full committee approval of major agriculture projects and Pennsylvania State University, July 17, 2001; 76.
      - Senators Specter and Santorum announce full committee approval of major agriculture projects for the Philadelphia area, July 17, 2001; 77.
      - Senator Specter's weekly radio conference, July 18, 2001; 78.
      - Senator Specter introduces interstate waste bill, July 18, 2001; 79.
      - Senator Specter announces funding for land and water conservation, July 19, 2001; 80.
      - Senator Specter announces funding for major projects in the Philadelphia area, July 19, 2001; 81.
      - Senators Specter and Santorum announce funding approval for Potter County sewer systems, July 20, 2001; 82.
      - Senators Specter and Santorum announce funding for Lehigh County projects, July 20, 2001; 83.
      - Senator Specter announces funding approval for Millerstown community building improvements, July 20, 2001; 84.
      - Senator Specter comments on latest developments in stem cell research, his interstate waste bill, U.S. Airways/United merger, and Bush's faith-based initiative, July 19, 2001; 85.
      - Senators Specter and Santorum announce funding for projects in the Philadelphia area, July 20, 2001; 86.
      - Senators Specter and Santorum announce funding for Lancaster area project, July 20, 2001; 87.
      - Dairy compact receives Judiciary Committee hearing, July 25, 2001; 88.
      - Senator Specter introduces Amish youth employment protection bill, July 25, 2001; 89.
      - Specter and Santorum announce approval of funds for the Erie courthouse, July 26, 2001; 90.
      - Specter and Santorum announce approval of funds for the Pittsburgh post office and courthouse, July 26, 2001; 91.
      - Senator Specter comments on DOJ decision re: United/U.S. Air, July 27, 2001; 92.
      - Senators Specter and Santorum announce funding approval for urban redevelopment and storm overflow management in Allegheny County, July 20, 2001; 93.
      - Senator Specter releases letter to President Bush on stem cells, July 20, 2001; 94.
      - Santorum and Specter announce funding to assist residents of Northside properties in Pittsburgh, July 20, 2001; 95.
      - Santorum and Specter announce $500,000 for Penn State public water systems technical assistance center, July 20, 2001; 96.
      - Santorum and Specter announce $3 million for child abuse prevention, July 20, 2001; 97.
      - Santorum and Specter announce $400,000 for National Association of Town Watch, July 20, 2001; 98.
      - Santorum and Specter announce $1.5 million for NASA program at Muhlenberg College, July 20, 2001; 99.
      - Senator Specter announces funding approval for Discovery Square, July 20, 2001; 100.
      - Specter announces new VA Medical Center in Pittsburgh, July 30, 2001; 101.
      - Specter announces $4.85 million grant for Three Rivers Wet Weather Program, July 31, 2001; 102.
    - August-December 2001 (Box 1224, Folder 4)
      - Specter comments on latest developments in Maglev, patients' bill of rights, stem cell research, and the Philadelphia school system, August 2, 2001; 1.
      - Specter comments on President's intent to nominate Patrick Meehan as U.S. Attorney, August 3, 2001; 2.
      - Senate bill naming courthouse after Cahn, August 3, 2001; 3.
      - Senator Specter comments on President's decision regarding stem cell research, August 9, 2001; 4.
      - Senators Specter and Santorum announce funding for Maglev project, August 15, 2001; 5.
      - Senator Specter comments on Senate floor regarding yesterday's terrorist attacks, September 12, 2001; 6.
      - Senator Specter comments on declaration of war, September 13, 2001; 7.
      - Senator Specter applauds confirmation of Patrick Meehan as U.S. Attorney, September 14, 2001; 8.
      - Senator Specter announces $1 million grant for United Way of southeastern Pennsylvania, September 17, 2001; 9.
      - Senator Specter announces renovations at the Lebanon Veterans Affairs Medical Center, September 17, 2001; 10.
      - Statement of Senator Arlen Specter on layoff of 11,000 U.S. Airways employees, September 17, 2001; 11.
      - Senator Specter introduces legislation to honor the passengers and crew of United Airlines flight 93 with Congressional Gold Medal, September 19, 2001; 12.
      - Senator Specter reacts to decision concerning Hollidaysburg car shops, September 19, 2001; 13.
      - Senator Specter comments on the President's address to the nation and Governor Ridge's appointment, September 21, 2001; 14.
      - Senator Specter reacts to President Bush's speech, September 20, 2001; 15.
      - Senator Specter testifies before the ITC investigative hearing regarding steel import crisis, September 25, 2001; 16.
      - Senator Specter appeals surface transportation board's decision to close Hollidaysburg car shops, September 28, 2001; 17.
      - Specter urges deliberate and swift action on antiterrorism legislation, October 3, 2001; 18.
      - Lieberman, Specter offer homeland defense legislation, October 11, 2001; 19.
      - Senator Specter comments on Department of Homeland Security, anti-terrorism legislation, the airport security bill, and stem cell research, October 11, 2001; 20.
      - Senator Specter gives testimony before Senate committee hearing on homeland security, October 12, 2001; 21.
      - Specter announces fiscal year 2002 funding levels for LHHS and education appropriations subcommittee, December 19, 2001; 22.
      - Senator Specter announces federal funding for northeast Pennsylvania projects, December 21, 2001; 23.
      - Senator Specter announces federal funding for central Pennsylvania projects, December 21, 2001; 24.
      - Senator Specter announces federal funding for Lehigh Valley projects, December 21, 2001; 25.
      - Senator Specter announces federal funding for Philadelphia area projects, December 21, 2001; 26.
      - Senator Specter announces federal funding for western Pennsylvania projects, December 21, 2001; 27.
    - January-June 2002 (Box 1224, Folder 5)
      - Senator Specter announces $3.3 million emergency grant for employees of airlines and airline related industries, January 9, 2002; 1.
      - Heilbrun joins Specter staff, January 17, 2002; 2.